Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design,Corcoran Gallery of Art education department records 1961-2010 COR0006.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Exhibitions [2016 processing project], 1960-2006; Series 18
  - Large-Print Brochures Hammer Collection, Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Hammer Collection Elementary Packets, Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Loose Brochures, Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Shaker Design, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Backhoff, Harry, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Surrogate Selves, 1989 January 24 April 16; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Wall Labels - "Amer. Impress. Prints", Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - La Vie Moderne: Label Set, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Surrealist Photographs, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Capital Campaign: Atrium Renovation Potentials / Strategies Overall, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Label/Project Foyer 1990-1991, Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Background Info for Atrium, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - CGA Atrium Labels, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - American Landscape Lunch / Seminar, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Terrie Sultan on Lurs in Collect. Cont. Art 1990, Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - State of Colls + Coll Wishes Frank Kelly's Ideass on Collections '89, 1989; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Salon Dor, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Image of Blacks, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Photographers in CGA's Coollection, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Writing on Multiculturalism Cornel West '92, 1992; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Richard Erbe Corresp., Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Archives Brochure '91, 1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Tour mobile / van DL '91, 1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - The Art Chronicles, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Community Contacts - Songs, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Geneological Research, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - The Hemicycle, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Perm Collection Labels, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Drafts Coll Labels, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Pomegranate Press Book P.C., Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Art Chronicles Evaluation, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Sabina OTT Portrait (Laurel), Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - David Bates Cottonmoutth, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Burgoyne Diller, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Lipski, Donald, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Cindy Sherman, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Tapestries (Loire) Label Info., Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - James Drake, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Randy Korn: Evaluation of Projs. '90, 1990; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - BSM Slide Lecture - American Coll., Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - American Art History Slide Lecture, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Luncheon Seminar Americans in Paris, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Summer Marketing Plans (1990), Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Realism in America, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Souvenir Book of Corcoran Thomas Hudson, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Draft - An American Landmark, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Reinstall. of Amer. Coll. Gall Brochure, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Gallery Redesignation 185-89, 1985; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Loose Documents, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Annual Report FY 88, 1985-1987; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Architectural Treasure Hunt, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Contemporary Art, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Pictures w/i Pictures, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Contract Photographers, 1988 December 5; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Interactive Video Research, Circa 1985-1991; Series 18 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - FY88-89 Italian Renaissance Majolica, 1989 April 16 - October 29; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - La Vie Moderne: 19th Century French Painting, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - FY88-89 Great Black Women, 1989 February 9 - March 26; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Fy90-91 James Peale, 1990 July 14 - September 16; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Black Photographers Bear Witness, 1990 January-March; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Carrie Mae Weems, 1988; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Facing History - Research, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Black Image - Labels, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Facing History Video, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Curatorial Procedures, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Homer Labels, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Rauschenberg Overseas Culture Interchange - Press Kit, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Winslow Homer - Labels, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Atrium: Quiz, labels, gallery talks, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Mythoplogy Book Copies, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Press Clippings, Etc., 1989-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Preston Powers Drafts, 1983; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - CGA American Neoclassical Sculpture Info., Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Southern Roads / City Pavements (Freeman) (1983), Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - People and Power: Portraits from the Federal Village, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Nigeria - Information - Extras (docent), Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Arthur B. Carles (1984), Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Images of the 70's: 9 Washington Artitsts, 1979; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Treasures of Ancient Nigeria Brochures, 1980 December 18 - 1981 January 31; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Nigerian Art - Symbolism, The Approach, Introduction, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Treasures of Ancient Nigeria - Orientation Gallery, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Guy Pne du Bois Brochures, Circa 1979-1990; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Spanish Art Tomorrow Brochures, 1981 October 14; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - The American West (1981), Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Circus Art Brochures, 1982 April-June; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Natural Settings, 1986 January 11 - March 2; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - The Generic Figure, 1986 March 8 - April 20; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Three Sculptors, 1987 May 9 - August 16; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Women at Work, 1987 May 16 - August 23; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - The Sun King, 1984 December 15 - 1985 April 7; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Roy Lichtenstein, 1988 September 17 - November 20; Series 18 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - A New World: Masterpieces of American Painting, 1760-1910, 1983 December 7 - 1984 February 12; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - American Masters Drawings, 1986; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - New World - Research, Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Asleson Research - New World, Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - French Reviews of New World, Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - New World Script Treatment New World Film Script Treatm., Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - August Sander: German Photography 83, 1983; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Northern Light: Scandinavian Ptg. Late 19th Century, Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Borofsky - Amy's Stuff, 1985; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - NEH Surrealism, Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Surrealist Photography '84, 1984; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Surrealist Photography Photography, 1984 February 22 - April 22; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Sun King Loose Info., Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Robert Motherwell Paintings, 1984 September-November; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - German Expressionism Paintings Summer 1984, Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Winslow HHomer Croquet scenes, 1984 July 14 - September 16; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Picturesque Views / Poetic Images, Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Black Folk Art, Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Black Folk Art: Teachers Pkt., Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Black Folk Art Program Development, Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Treasurers of Ancient Nigeria info, Circa 1980; Series 18 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Brochures: Odyssey, Robert Henry, Henri's Circle, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Loose Documents, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Odyssey: The Art of Photography - press kit, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Armand Hammer Coll.: Five Cent. of Masterpieces - press kit, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Armand Hammer Coll.: 5 Cent. of Masterpieces info., Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Of Time and Place - complete sample packet, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Of Time and Place - slides and brochures, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Facing History - press kit, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Ed. Dept. - Black Folk Art in America, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - African Americans: A Self-Portrait - press kit, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - CGA African Explores - press kit, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - We The People - press kit, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - The Sun King - press kit, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Hispanic Art in the US, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Facing History, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - I Dream A World, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Discover the Corcoran Tours and Workshops Poster, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Architecture is Elementary, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Motherwell Brochure, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - The Sun King (1984-1985), Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - A New World (1983-1984), Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - 38th Corcoran Biennial (1983), Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Lecture & Program Info for a New World, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Family Portrait Day Workshop May 1981, 1981 May; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Georges Vantongerlo (1980), Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - American Masters Brochures, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Discover the Corcoran '89 Posters, 1989; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - A New World Masterpieces of American Painting, Circa 1988; Series 18 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - African Explores Training Materials, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - African Explores: Lecture by Elizabeth Roark, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - African Explores: Teachers' Evaluation, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - African Explores Slides, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - African Explores: Teachers Packets, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - African Explores: Brochures + Pamphlets, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Visiones of Pueblo - press kits, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Teacher's Workshop, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Docent Training Materian for Visiones, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Visiones del Pueblo packets for press, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - press packets, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - press packets, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Special Tours: African Explores / Visiones del Pueblo, Circa 1993; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Visiones del Pueblo Teacher Package's Slides, 1993 August-October; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - African Explores - program budget, Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - American Neoclassical Sculpture at CGA - Brochure, Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Archibald J. Motley, Jr., Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Songs of My People Packets, Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Time Sheets, Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - "Songs of My People" Comments, Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Facing History - Letters + Comments, Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Songs of My People Confirmation Letters, Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Random Exhibit Information, Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Black Photographers Bear Witness Exhibition Labels, Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Facing History - Labels, Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Facing History - Exhibition Checklist, Circa 1989-1991; Series 18 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Checklist/Text, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Grants/Budget, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Odyssey - press kit, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Checklist/Text, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Stiefel, 1985 September 6; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Grants/Budget Niagara, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Niagara Press Release / Publication, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Resource / Films Niagara, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Research Nat'l. Museum of Amer. Art, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Checklist/Text Hispanic Art, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Hispanic Aart, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Mural Workshop Education Components, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Grants/Budget Hispanic Art, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Public Programs, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Press Release / Publication, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Research PAZ, Octavio, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Resource / Films, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Check List Odyssey, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Checklist/Text Nat'l. Geo., Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence Nat. Geo., Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Grants/Budget Nat. Geo., Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Press Release / Publication, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Public Programs Nat. Geo., Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Resource / Films Nat. Geo., Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Statistics Nat. Geo., Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Checklist/Text, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence I Dream A World, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Education Components The Black Aesthetic, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Grants/Budget I Dream A World, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Press Release / Publication I Dream A World, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Research, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Resource/Films, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Music: A Hand is on the Gate, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Ethnic Notions Vid., Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Photo Blow-Ups, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Facing History Press, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Consultants / Consultant Work / Grant Proposal, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Facing Hisitory - Film Series, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Object Labels / Images / Content Room, Circa 1985-1990; Series 18 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Checklist/Text Songs of My People, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Songs of My People, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Songs of My People Education Components, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Songs of My People Grants/Budget, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Songs of My People Press Release / Publication, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Songs of My People Public Programs, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Songs of My People Resource / Film, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Songs of My People Sites / Exhibition Travel, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Songs of My People Statistics, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Andy Warhol Checklist, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Doug Shawn, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Family Day 1992, Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Grants/Budget Disney + Warhol, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Press Release / Publication Disney + Warhol, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Resource / Films Warhol + Disney, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Motley Checklist/Text, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Motley Correspondence, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Family Day Budget, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Motley Grants and Budgets, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Motley Press Release / Publication, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Motley Public Progrmas, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Motley Resource/Films, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Motley Press Kit, 1991 October 23; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Motley Exhibition Overview, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Africa Explores Checklist/Text, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Africa Explores Correspondence, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Africa Explores Africa Explores, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Family Day Folk Art of Latin America, 1993 August 14 - October 10; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Africa Explores Grant/Budget, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Press Release/Publications, 1990-1993; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Africa Explores + Visiones Public Programs, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Africa Explores + Visiones Resource/Film, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Visiones Checklist/Text, 1993 February; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence Folk Art of Latin America, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Education Components Visiones Del Pueblo, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Family Day Visiones Del Pueblo + Latin America, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Public Programs Visiones + Latin America, 1993; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Grants/Budget Folk Art of Latin America, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Visiones Del Pueblo Press Release/Publications, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Day of the Dead Resource/Films, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Research: Folk Art of Latin America, Visiones, Black Folk Art in America, Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Visiones Loose Documents (1), 1993 June; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Visiones Loose Documents (2), 1993 May-June; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Visiones Loose Documents (3), Circa 1992-1994; Series 18 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - CGA Programs Loose Information (1), Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - CGA Programs Loose Information (2), Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Century Association, 1993 July 16 - September 13; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Borofsky Exhibition Guide, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Asafo Flags, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - I Dream A World Materials, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - I Dream A World Materials, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Motley Packet, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - FY91 Winslow Homer & Circle, 1991 March 16 - May 12; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - American Art American Vision, 1993 April 24 - July 11; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Folk Art of Latin America, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Kreeger House, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Kiki Smith - Zizi Raymond, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - The Artist as Illustrator, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Salgado, 1990-1992; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Lou Stovall, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Antony Gormley, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Songs of My People, 1992; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Archibald Motley, Jr., Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Archibald Motley, Jr. For Docent Study Tour Givers, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Still Working Info., Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - FY91 Robert Rauschenburg, 1990-1991; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Worthington Whittredge (training), Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Hispanic Contemporary Art in the U.S., Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Sport in Art, 1991 September 21 - December 8; Series 18 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Paramount News Clip "A Freedoms Set Key for Bond Drive", Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Norman Rockwell's World... An American Dream, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Norman Rockwell Version I, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Ruby Bridges, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - "60 Minute Loop Rockwell", Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Rockwell Audio CD, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Chicago Rockwell Audio CD, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Norman Rockwell: Pictures for the American People Tape, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Norman Rockwell: Pictures for the American People Tape, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Norman Rockwell: Pictures for the American People Resource Packet for Educations, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Norman Rockwell Programming, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Norman Rockwell Exhibition Information, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - [Rockwell Report], 2000 September; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Contracts, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Norman Rockwell: Groups/Ticketing, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Admissions/Tickets, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Attendance/Sales, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Norman Rockwell, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Rockwell: Press Clippings Etc, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Rockwell: Special Events, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Norman Rockwell, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Rockwell: Publications, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Norman Rockwell: Programs, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Membership, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Rockwell: Checklist Installatoin, Circa 2000; Series 18 (Box 28, Folder 25)